James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1982-2010; 4
  - 77th Session, 2000-2002; 4
    - House Bills, 2001-2002; 2
      - HB 2387, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - HB 2387, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - HB 2560, Imposition Of Community Supervision On A Defendant Convicted Of A State Jail Felony, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - HB 2560, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - HB 2560, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - HB 2560, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - HB 2561, Creating The Criminal Offense Of Misapplication Of The Property Of A Charter School, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - HB 2561, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - HB 2561, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - HB 2562, Adoption Of Rules Of Civil Procedure By Supreme Court, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - HB 2562, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - HB 2562, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - HB 2562, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - HB 2563, Air And Water By Persons Selling Motor Vehicle Fluid, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - HB 2563, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - HB 2563, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - HB 2563, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - HB 2563, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - HB 2564, School Finance- Set Asides, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - HB 2564, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - HB 2564, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - HB 2564, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - HB 2565, Funding Program For Students With Disabilities, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - HB 2565, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - HB 2565, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - HB 2565, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - HB 2565, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - HB 2566, Worker’s Compensation Appeal, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - HB 2566, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - HB 2566, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - HB 2566, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - HB 2699, Protection Of Water Quality From Animal Feeding Operations, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - HB 2699, Amendments, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - HB 2889, Attorneys And Law Clerks, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - HB 2889, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - HB 2889, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - HB 2889, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - HB 2912, Water Quality, General (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - HB 2912, Water Quality, General (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - HB 2912, Water Quality, Amendment (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - HB 2912, Water Quality, Amendment (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - HB 2912, Amendments, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - HB 2922, Obstructing Railroad Crossing With Train, General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - HB 2922, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - HB 2922, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - HB 2922, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - HB 2922, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - HB 3027, Resident Tuition For Nonresident Students, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - HB 3028, State Science And Engineering Fair, General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - HB 3028, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - HB 3028, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - HB 3028, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - HB 3028, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - HB 3029, Defense Fees And Liability Issues, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - HB 3030, Performance Data Of Students, General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - HB 3030, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - HB 3030, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - HB 3030, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - HB 3030, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - HB 3310, Payment Sources For School District, General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - HB 3310, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - HB 3310, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - HB 3310, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - HB 3310, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - HB 3311, Creation Of Judicial District Composed Of McLennan County, General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - HB 3311, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - HB 3312, Emergency Medical Dispatch Resource Centers, General, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - HB 3312, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - HB 3312, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - HB 3312, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - HB 3312, Talking Points, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HB 3313, Elementary Class Size, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HB 3313, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - HB 3313, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - HB 3313, Conferee Discharge Notice, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - HB 3313, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - HB 3313, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - HB 3314, Theft Of Livestock From A Commission Merchant, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - HB 3314, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - HB 3344, Attorneys Employed Or Contracted To Insurers, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - HB 3344, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - HB 3344, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - HB 3344, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - HB 3387, Disposition Of Public Property In A Defense Economic Readjustment Zone, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - HB 3387, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - HB 3387, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - HB 3387, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - HB 3387, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - HB 3395, Standards For Credentialing Of Health Care Providers, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - HB 3395, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - HB 3395, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - HB 3395, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - HB 3395, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - HB 3561, Prohibition Of Disclosure Of Defense Council’s Fee Statement, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - HB 3562, Authority To Enforce Laws Protecting Water Quality, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - HB 3562, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - HB 3562, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - HB 3563, Unauthorized Practice Of Law By Liability Insurers, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - HB 3563, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - HB 3563, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - HB 3563, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - HB 3563, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - HB 3691, Creation Of West Medical Center, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - HB 3691, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - HB 3691, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - HB 3691, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - HB 3691, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Senate Bills, 2001; 3
      - SB 19, Improvement Of Children’s Health In Public Schools, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - SB 19, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - SB 19, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - SB 19, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - SB 19, Committee Remarks, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - SB 216 Expand Use Of Telecommunication Infrastructure Fund (TIF), General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 46)
      - SB 216, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - SB 216, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - SB 216, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - SB 975, Texas Virtual Charter School, General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - SB 975, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - SB 1210, Attorneys and Law Clerks, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - SB 1653, 1654, Liability Insurance, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 53)
      - SB 1653, 1654, Texas Association of Defense Counsel (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - SB 1653, 1654, Texas Association of Defense Counsel (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Joint Resolutions, 2001-2002; 4
      - HCR 332, Re: HB 6, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - HJR 44, Other Taxing Units to Exempt Travel Trailers from ad Valorem Taxes, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - HJR 60, Rulemaking Power Of Supreme Court, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - HJR 60, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - HJR 60, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - HJR 60, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Commemoratives and Commendations, 2001; 5
      - HCR 299, Central Texas Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - HR 946, Miller, Jana, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - HR 1029, Central Texas Chapters Of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - A. Philip Randolph Institute, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - City Of West, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Cottle, Richard Dale, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Dixon, George Davis, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Everett, A.L., Jr., 2001 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Fisher, Phil “Fish”, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Hawkins, Robert, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Jones, Vivian, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Neal, Ada M., 2001 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Oldham, Johnnie Benjamin, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Permission Granted To Professor Janice C. May & Students To Use The House Chamber, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Randolph, Asa Phillip, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Recognize February 8, 2001 as West Day (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Reicher Catholic High School, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - St. Mary’s Catholic School, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - St. Mary’s Elementary School, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Vandiver, J.B., Sr., 2001 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Topical, 2000-2002; 6
      - Animal Cruelty, 2001 February-May (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Bingo, 2001 February (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Bosque Watershed, 2001 January-May (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Brazos Landing Townhomes, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Celebrate Freedom Week, 2001 May (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Charter Schools, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Child Care Services, 2001 March (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Class Size Waiver, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Committee on Public Education, Interim Report, 2000 December (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Construction Of State Loop 574, 2001 March-April (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Dental Care, 2001 April-May (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - Department Of Aging, 2000-2002 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - Education, General, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - Education, Equal Education Opportunity, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - Education, Finance Policy, Southwest Educational Development Laboratory (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Education, Finance Policy, Southwest Educational Development Laboratory (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Education, Funding, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Election, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Employees Retirement System of Texas, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Financial Disclosure By Municipal Officers, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Fire Departments, Marlin, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Food & Beverages In Vending Machines On Public School Campuses, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Graduated Driver Licensing, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Health Care, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Health Care, ABC, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Health Insurance For Public School Employees, 2001 March-April (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Payment Of Healthcare Providers, 2001 May 22-25 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Private School Vouchers, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Public Education (1 of 2), 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Public Education (2 of 2), 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Public Education, Statistics, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Same Sex Marriage, 2001 March-May (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Taxpayer For Equal Appraisal, 2002 January (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Texas Commission on Environmental Quality, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Texas Credit Union, 2001 March (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Texas State Cemetery, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Texas State Technical College, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Urban Affairs Committee, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Veterans’ Care, 2001 May 8 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Waco Pollution, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - West ISD, 2002 February (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - 78th Session, 2001-2004, undated; 5
    - General, 2003-2004; 1
      - Attendance and Voting Record, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Attorney General’s Legislative Staff Briefing, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, Congratulatory Re-election Letters, 2002 November (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Democratic Voting Block, 2003 January-February (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - End of Session Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Finance Proposals and Estimates, 2003, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - House Committee on Calendars, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Kerry Campaign, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Legislative Reference Library, 2003 January 21 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Motion to Limit Amendments, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Photo Index of the 78th Legislature, c. 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Proposed Changes to the House Rules of Procedure, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Public Policy, Research Reports, 2004 March (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Record Votes, HB 1, 2003 April 15 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Record Votes, HB 4 (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Record Votes, HB 4 (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Record Votes, HB 4 (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Record Votes, HB 7, 2003 April 14 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Record Votes, HB 15, 2003 April 28 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Report of the Texas Legislature, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Representative Dunnam’s House Floor To-Do List, 2003 May 28 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Sunset Legislation Status Report, 2003 January 31 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Texas Constitution, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Texas Ethics Commission Nominations, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - House Bills, 2002-2003, undated; 2
      - Bill Draft, Appeal From Issuance Of Protective Order, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Bill Draft, Appeal Of Court Orders And Judgments Relating To Arbitration, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Bill Draft, Attorneys And Law Clerks Employed By A Court, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Bill Draft, Continuation And Functions Of The Texas Department Of Housing And Community Affairs, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Bill Draft, Harassment By Individuals Confined In Juvenile Detention Or Correctional Facilities, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Bill Draft, Composition OF The First And Fourteenth Courts For Appeals Districts, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Bill Draft, Continuation Of The Texas State Affordable Housing Corporation (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Bill Draft, Continuation Of The Texas State Affordable Housing Corporation (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Bill Draft, Continuation Of The Texas State Affordable Housing Corporation (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Bill Draft, Defendant’s Right To Appeal, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Bill Draft, Oversight Of Public Access To Supreme Court And Court Of Criminal Appeals, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Bill Draft, Peremptory Challenge Of A Juror In A Criminal Case, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Bill Draft, Pretrial Proceedings Involving Motions To Suppress Confessions Or Illegally Obtained Evidence, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Bill Draft, Prohibition Of Disclosure Of Defense Council’s Billing Statements By Insurers, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Bill Draft, Prohibiting Smoking, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Bill Draft, Punishment For Escape By Juveniles Detained In Secure Detention Or Correctional Facility, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Bill Draft, Release Of Confidential Information Of A Patient By Physician, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Bill Draft, Requirement To Provide Air And Water For Motor Vehicles, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Bill Analysis, Restricting The Disclosure Of Military Discharge Records, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - HB 1, Education, Amendments, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - HB 2, Impact On School Districts, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - HB 3, Health Care, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - HB 3, 2nd and 3rd Readings, 2003 September (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - HB 4, Amendments, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - HB 4, Background and Amendments (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - HB 4, Background and Amendments (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - HB 4, House Committee on Civil Practices (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - HB 4, House Committee on Civil Practices (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - HB 4, Legislator Conflicts, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - HB 4, Medical Malpractice Articles, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - HB 4, Talking Points, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - HB 7, State Government Reform, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - HB 12, 3rd Reading, Final Passage, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - HB 15, Abortion, Committee Report and Analysis, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - HB 16, 3rd Reading, Final Passage, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - HB 41, Application Of Franchise Tax, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - HB 275, Prosecution Of Theft Of Service, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - HB 568, Forced Annexation, Bill Support, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - HB 588, Uniform Admission and Reporting Procedures for Institutions of Higher Education, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - HB 604, Public School Finance, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - HB 675/SB 271, Regulation of Riding Stables, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - HB 676, Continuation Of The Texas department Of Housing And Community Affairs, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - HB 677, Continuation And Function Of The Texas Council On Purchasing From People With Disabilities, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - HB 749, Discharge Of Criminal Proceeding Because Of Delay In Prosecution, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - HB 786, Contents And Appeal Of Orders In A Suit Affecting Parent-Child Relationship, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - HB 787, Punishment For The Offense Of Passing A School Bus, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - HB 788, Penalty For Operating Motor Vehicle With A Driver’s License, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - HB 1181/SB 273, Court Reporters Certification Board, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - HB 1182, Creation Of A McLennan County Judicial District, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - HB 1183, Defendant’s Right To Appeal, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - HB 1184, Expert Reports Filed In Health Care Liability Claims, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - HB 1218, Texas State Board of Public Accountancy, Amendments, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - HB 1366, Environmental Regulation of Dry Cleaning Facilities, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - HB 1384, Termination Of Agreements With Insurance Agents (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - HB 1384, Termination Of Agreements With Insurance Agents (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - HB 1673, Questioning Prospective Jurors During Voir Dire Examinations, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - HB 1790, Architecture, Tape Transcription, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - HB 2165, Sentencing Procedure In Capital Felony Cases, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - HB 2166, Sentencing Procedure In Capital Felony Cases, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - HB 2204, Continuation And Functions Of The Texas State Affordable Housing Corporation, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - HB 3041, School Bus Safety Standards, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - HB 3110, Distribution Of Organ Donor Cards, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - HB 3111, Protections Of Consumer With Regard To The Action Of A Debt Collector, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - HB 3112, Provision Of Alcoholic Beverages To Person Under 18 Years Of Age, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - HB 3113, Definition of Child Abuse, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - HB 3114, Definition Of Gross Income Under Texas Family Code, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - HB 3115, Liability Of A Criminal Defendant, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - HB 3317, Enhancement Of Punishment In Criminal Cases, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - HB 3588, Texas Transportation Commission, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Senate Bills, 2003; 3
      - SB 261, Texas Council on Purchasing from People with Disabilities, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - SB 282, Continuation And Functions Of The Texas State Board Of Plumbing Examiners (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - SB 282, Continuation And Functions Of The Texas State Board Of Plumbing Examiners (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - SB 310, Insurance Data Collection, Talking Points, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - SB 310, Vote Analysis, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - SB 1067/SJR 42, Home-ownership, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - SB 1147, State Office of Administrative Hearings, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - SB 1466, Hotel Occupancy Taxes And Convention Center Financing, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - SB 1551, Creation Of Judicial Districts, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Joint Resolutions, 2002-2003; 4
      - CSHJR 3, Constitutional Amendments Calendar, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Dunnam Oath of Office, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - HJR 3, Texas Retirement System, General, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - HR 5, House Rules, Amendments, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - HJR 13, Prohibiting Judicial Candidates From Accepting Political Contributions, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Suspending Limitations on Conference Committee Jurisdiction, HB 1, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Suspending Limitations on Conference Committee Jurisdiction, HB 7, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Suspending Limitations on Conference Committee Jurisdiction, HB 24, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Suspending Limitations on Conference Committee Jurisdiction, HB 28, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Commemoratives & Commendations, 2002-2003; 5
      - HCR 67, GENCO Federal Credit Union, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - HCR 87, Smith James Allen, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - HCR 202, Recognition Of May 1, 2003 as Law Day In Texas, 2003 April 29 (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - HR 98, Madison County, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - HR 99, 125th Anniversary Westphalia, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - HR 100, Marian High School In Madisonville, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - HR123, Calvert High School Football Team, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - HR 124, Leon High School Lady Cougars, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - HR 158, Members Of The 143rd Infantry, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - HR 159, Bellmead Calvary Baptist Church’s 50th Anniversary, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - HR 249, Recognizing October 16, 2004 As Madisonville Mushroom Festival Day, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - HR 249, McKee, Patricia “Pat”, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - HR 1704, Cunningham, Sharon, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - SR 6, Rosebudd-Lott Cougars, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - Law Suit Against Texas A&M University-Commerce, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 32)
      - Amendment to Rule 3, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Topical, 2001-2004; 6
      - Bribery, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 34)
      - Business, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 35)
      - Clean Coal Technology, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 36)